<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Himalayan Asia Management Consulting Service</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Himalayan Asia Management Consulting Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sip &amp; Sustain: Water Security For The Philippines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/24-03-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/24-03-07/</guid>
      <description>Himalayan Asia participates in the event of AmCham Philippines hosting the “Sip &amp;amp; Sustain: Water Security for the Philippines” event on March 7, 2024.&#xA;This gathering brought together esteemed government figures, industry leaders, and Non-Government Organizations (NGOs) to emphasize the critical role of sound water management in achieving a water-secured global community. The event aligned with the theme of “Leveraging Water for Peace” and aimed to address water security challenges in the Philippines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Himalayan Asia attends the very 1st India – Philippines Tech Summit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/24-03-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/24-03-05/</guid>
      <description>The Embassy of India, Manila hosted the 1st ever India-Philippines Tech Summit (IPTS 2024) on 5 March 2024 at Shangri-La The Fort, Manila, Philippines.&#xA;The event is being organized in partnership with the Ministry of Electronics and Information Technology (MeitY) of India and the Federation of Indian Chambers of Commerce &amp;amp; Industry (FICCI) on the Indian side, and the Department of Information &amp;amp; Communication Technology (DICT) and the Philippines Chamber of Commerce &amp;amp; Industry (PCCI) from the Philippines side.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
