<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Himalayan Asia Management Consulting Service</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Himalayan Asia Management Consulting Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sip &amp; Sustain: Water Security For The Philippines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/24-03-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/24-03-07/</guid>
      <description>Himalayan Asia participates in the event of AmCham Philippines hosting the “Sip &amp;amp; Sustain: Water Security for the Philippines” event on March 7, 2024.&#xA;This gathering brought together esteemed government figures, industry leaders, and Non-Government Organizations (NGOs) to emphasize the critical role of sound water management in achieving a water-secured global community. The event aligned with the theme of “Leveraging Water for Peace” and aimed to address water security challenges in the Philippines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Himalayan Asia attends the very 1st India – Philippines Tech Summit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/24-03-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/24-03-05/</guid>
      <description>The Embassy of India, Manila hosted the 1st ever India-Philippines Tech Summit (IPTS 2024) on 5 March 2024 at Shangri-La The Fort, Manila, Philippines.&#xA;The event is being organized in partnership with the Ministry of Electronics and Information Technology (MeitY) of India and the Federation of Indian Chambers of Commerce &amp;amp; Industry (FICCI) on the Indian side, and the Department of Information &amp;amp; Communication Technology (DICT) and the Philippines Chamber of Commerce &amp;amp; Industry (PCCI) from the Philippines side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trash Situation and the Extended Producer Responsibility Act of 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/22-01-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 13:06:26 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/22-01-26/</guid>
      <description>The Philippine Congress passed the Extended Producer Responsibility Act last year as a response to the worsening trash situation in the country.&#xA;The Trash Situation Before 2022 The Philippines was ranked as the third worst plastic dumper in the oceans, just behind China and Indonesia.&#xA;The Philippines’ topmost garbage source is currently single-use plastic from sachets and food packaging such as coffee, noodles, snacks, and other food items.&#xA;In the National Solid Waste Management Commission’s 10-year report, the Philippines reached more than 18 million metric tons in 2020 from 13 million metric tons in 2008.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Geological Surveying?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/21-01-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/21-01-19/</guid>
      <description>Geological surveying is the systematic investigation of the geology beneath a piece of land. It is used to create a geological map or model.&#xA;This model can then be used for exploration, land-use planning, water resource assessment, geohazard and many others.&#xA;Assessment of silica fields for quarrying Assessment of silica fields for quarrying for industrial and medical use in Doña Remedios Trinidad, Bulacan&#xA;Mineral Resource Assessment Mineral Resource Assessment takes the identification, surveys, and development of minerals as part of the supply for the continuing &#34;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Forest Biodiversity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/21-03-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/21-03-02/</guid>
      <description>World Wildlife Day is on the 3rd of March and it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand why we have to remind people annually of the importance of forests which serves as the home for wildlife.&#xA;What is Forest Biodiversity and Why is it Important? Forests cover about 30% of the planet’s land surface and with the demise of forests from fires and deforestation, the numbers are continuously going down. If these numbers keep up, rainforests will be gone in 80 years or so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primer on Establishing a Sanitary Landfill</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/21-02-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/21-02-23/</guid>
      <description>Establishing a sanitary landfill (SLF)is on the government’s topmost plan to curb the worsening issue of improper garbage disposal everywhere.&#xA;Careful planning is necessary, and we came up with this primer to dispel any misconceptions about establishing an SLF in your community.&#xA;What is a sanitary landfill and Why do we need it?? A sanitary landfill (SLF) is a safe site for communities to dump their wastes so they don’t end up in farmlands and oceans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elements of Environmental Planning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/21-02-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/21-02-09/</guid>
      <description>Environmental planning facilitates decision-making to carry out development considering the natural environmental, social, political, economic, and governance factors. It provides a holistic framework to achieve sustainable outcomes.&#xA;Socio-economic Development Environmental planning is all about its inhabitants. Why do we need to plan if it is just for buildings anyway?&#xA;Socio-economic development means every part of the society is considered, not just the investors but, more importantly, the stakeholders in the affected community.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
